# CHRISTIAN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### CONTACT



3163746523



christian-lazo-u@hotmail.com



/Christianlazo11



/christian-lazo-u/



christianlazoportfolio.netlif y.app/

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- BOOTSTRAP
- TAILWIND
- FIGMA
- GIT
- REACT
- ANGULAR
- NODEJS
- JAVA
- MONGODB
- MYSOL

# **ENGLISH**

B1

### **PROFILE**

I am a web developer with experience in projects focused on responsive design and accessibility. Student in training as a technician in programming applications and cloud services. I have participated in programming bootcamps and have developed both client-side and server-side web applications using Scrum and Git version control methodologies.

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

### **Escape Room**

01/05/2022 - 03/06/2022

Application created for the EducaMás foundation, with the purpose of filtering the students who present themselves, by means of two tests, one of logical tests and the other of code.

https://github.com/Christianlazo11/Frontend Escape Room.git

### Migrantes 2022 Freelancer

10/01/2022 - 25/03/2022

App developed for self-employed client Desing and development of a user panel and surveys Development with AngularJs, Bootstrap, NodeJs, scrum methodology

https://github.com/Christianlazo11/Frontend Migrantes.git

### Distrifiestas & Piñatas Educa Más

10/02/2022 - 15/03/2022

Ecommerce development for a balloon warehouse Desing and development of a user interface and prototyping Development with ReactJs, Bootstrap, NodeJs, Scrum methodology

https://github.com/Christianlazo11/Frontend DyP.git

### **EDUCATION**

### **Diploma in Programming**

Mintic - Universidad de Caldas 01/05/2021 - 15/12/2021

### **Bootcamp Full-Stack Developer**

Programate-EducaMás 06/12/2021 - 03/06/2022

# **Application Programming and Cloud Services Technician**

01/10/2021 - 15/12/2022